ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 15, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Viewpoint; Multinational Corporations - Trading U.S. Jobs for Coporate Profit, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    By Industrial Union Department. v.5:no.4 (1975:Fourth Quarter). Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Challenge of Internationalization, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Box: 15, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Multinational Corporations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By AFL-CIO Economic Research Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Multinational Corporations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Multinational Corporations; Expanding Influence in the 1990s, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: One World - But Which One?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By ICEF (International Federation of Chemical, Engery and General Workers' Unions). Item is in English.
- Box: 15, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1990-1991, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    By Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladoras. Volume 2, Number 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladoras, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    By Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladoras. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Maquiladora; Standards of Conduct, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Box: 15, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Global Free Trade and Gatt, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By James Goldsmith. Extract from the book Le Piege by James Goldsmith, updated and translated into English. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Global Village vs. Global Pillage; A One-World Strategy for Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Jermy Brecher and Tim Costello. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Trade; Where We Stand, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labour Issues Quarterly; Aspects of the Japanese Work Place Internationalization of Japanese Corporates, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By The Japan Institute of Labour, The Ministry of Labour. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Common Interests of Employees and Employers in the 1990s; Competing in the Global Market: The challenge to Buisness and Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Economic Policy Council of the United Nations Association of the USA. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Free Trade Union Institute, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Trade; How International Trade Keeps the Third World Poor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By World Development Movement. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Southern Africa Perspectives: Black Unions in South Afica, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    By Sandy Boyer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Southern Africa Perspectives: Human rights Violations in Apartheid South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    By Gail Hovey. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Southern Africa Perspectives: South Africa Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    By Richard Leonard. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: South Africa Labor News: Report of the AFL-CIO delegation to South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.2:no.1 (1983:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: South Africa Labor News: The Challenege of Black Trade Unions in South America, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.1:no.2 (1982:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: South Africa Labor News: The Challenge of Black Trade Unions in South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.1:no.2 (1982:May). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: South Africa Labor News: The rising tide of black opposition to Apartheid, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.1:no.3 (1982:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: South Africa Labor News: What does the AFL-CIO stand for?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.1:no.4 (1982:Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: South Africa Labor News: What does the AFL-CIO stand for?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.1:no.4 (1982:Sept.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Suoth Africa labor News: Report of the AFL-CIO delegations to South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By The African-American Labor Center. v.2:no.1 (1983:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: "TheYear that Shook the Garment Industry": Take forward our Living Wage Campaign in 1989, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    By GAWU (Garment and Allied Workers' Union (S.A.)). 1st Anniversary. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constructive Change in South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By Robert R Tusenius. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: South Africa: Nation on Trial, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    By Family Protection Scoreboard. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Birth of COSATU, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By Learn and Teach. Learn and Teach, no.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Practice of Solidarity, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By John Hudson. Photocopy from Democratic Left (1990:Sep./Oct.), pp.33-45. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 1978: International Year Against Apartheid, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A Crime Against Humanity: Questions and Answers on Apartheid in Souther Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By United Nations. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Apartheid and Labor: A Critical Review of the Effects on Labor Matters in South Africa, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Apartheid For Export?: South African Transational Corporations Aboard, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Apartheid For Export?: South African Transational Corporations Aboard, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Apartheid For Export?: South African Transnational Corporations Aboard, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Apartheid: The Facts, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By United Nations and international Defence and Aid Fund for Southern Africa. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Investment in Apartheid, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. List of Companies with Investment and Interest in South Afrca. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Trade Unions Against Apartheid, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Box: 16, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Black Labor As a Swing factor in South Africa's Evolution, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Roy Godson. International Labor Program Papers, no.3. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: An Injury to One is an Injury to All, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
    By COSATU (Congress of South African Trade Unions). AFL-CIO Executive Council meeting 21 February 1991. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Shop Stewards Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.1:no.2 (1990:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Shop Stewards Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). no.4 (1991:Sept.). Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Conference Proceedings from Stabilizing democray in South Africa: the Challenges of post Apartheid Development, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By Southern Africa Grantmakers' Affinity Group. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: South African Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Institute for Industrial Education. v.1:no.1 (1974:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: South African Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Institute for Industrial Education. v.11:no.4 (1986:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: South African Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Institute for Industrial Education. v.15:no.6 (1991:Mar.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: South African Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Institute for Industrial Education. v.15:no.6 (1991:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: South African Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Institute for Industrial Education. v.15:no.6 (1991:Mar.). Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 16, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Offical Trade Union Drectory and Industrial Relations Handbook, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    By TUCSA (Trade Union Council of South Africa). Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: SACTWU News, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.15 (1991:Sep. 5). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sactwu News, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.14 (1991:Aug. 22). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Sactwu News, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.11 (1991:July 11). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: SACTWU News, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.4:no.15 (1992:Nov. 19). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: SACTWU News, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.5:no.14 (1993:Nov. 5). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.7 (1991:May 1). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.6 (1991:Apr. 18). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.5 (1991:Apr. 4). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.4 (1991:Mar. 212). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.1 (1991:Feb. 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.3 (1991:Mar. 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.2 (1991:Feb. 21). Newspaper. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.3:no.2 (1991:Feb. 21). Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Shopsteward: COSATU Special Congress, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    By COSATU (Congress of South African Trade Unions). 10-12 September 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.9 (1990:June 20). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.1:no.4 (1989:Dec. 6). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.7 (1990:May 9). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.1:no.1 (1989:Oct. 18). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.6 (1990:Apr. 11). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.10 (1990:July 16). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.4 (1990:Mar. 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.10 (1990:July 16). Newspaper. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.11 (1990:Aug. 13). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.13 (1990:Sep. 26). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.14 (1990:Oct. 14). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.8 (1990:May 30). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.3 (1990:Feb. 28). Publisher adjusted issue numbering. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.6 (1990:Feb. 14). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.2:no.5 (1990:Jan. 31). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.1:no.3 (1989:Nov. 15). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: SACTWU, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). v.1:no.2 (1989: Nov. 1). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: SACTWU: Launching Congress Special, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    By SACTWU (South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union). September 1989. Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.21 (1988:June 17). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.19 (1988). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.22 (1988:June 24). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.23 (1988:July 1). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.24 (1988:July 8). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.10:no.20 (1988:June 10). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.29 (1989:Aug. 4). Publisher mis-numbered. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.22 (1989:June 23). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.17 (1989: May 19). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.23 (1989:June 30). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.24 (1989:July 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.25 (1989:July 14). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.26 (1989:July 21). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.35 (1989:Sep. 22). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.27 (1989:July 28). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.21 (1989:June 16). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.29 (1989:Aug. 11). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.31 (1989:Aug. 25). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.33 (1989:Sep. 8). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.34 (1989:Sep. 15). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.30 (1989:Aug. 18). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.18 (1989: May 26). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.19 (1989:June 2). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.32 (1989:Sep. 1). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.11 (1989: Apr. 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.12 (1989: Apr. 14). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.13 (1989: Apr. 21). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.20 (1989:June 9). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.14 (1989: Apr. 28). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Clothes Line (Western Cape Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.11:no.15/16 (1989: May 12). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Clothes Line: First Anniversary Issue, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.1 (1988:May 13). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.2 (1988:June 3). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.3 (1988:July 4). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.6 (1988:Sep. 7). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.7 (1988:Sep. 21). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.1:no.9 (1988:Nov. 8). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.1 (1989:Feb. 13). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.3 (1989:Apr. 6). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.4 (1989:Apr. 26). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.5 (1989:May 19). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.7 (1989:July 12). Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Clothes Line (Napal Region), Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    By Garment and Allied Workers Union of S.A. v.2:no.9 (1989:Aug. 17). Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Accordo Integrativo Valsesiano ai C.C.N.L. per gli addetti all'industria della lana, maglie-calze e tessili vari del 19 dicembre 1988, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
    By Associazione Industriali Valsesia. Photocopy. Item is in Italian.
  - Item 2: Contratto Collettivo Nazionale Di Lavoro, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Box: 17, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Changing the World Through Equality: The Trade Union Vision, Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
    By ICFTU. Photocopy. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)